how's it going everyone came as 15 here
with a very special video today so as a
lot of you may know I have a bottle of
the costume right here I'll show you in
a minute as you can see I got my Bobby
costume right there now a lot of you
also know find all of you because I
don't really want that much I also have
a sock the Hedgehog costume which i
don't really know what's out right that
moans I sorry but I really can't show
you but I I just touch to have a little
update video four minutes huh a lot of
Manic fans will be excited about this
I'm actually making a Manic costume next
as you can see I I already caught the
body here some places for the arms the
head the other and as you can see I use
yellow paper mache for no no not paper
mache just yellow pieces of paper for
the body in the head and so far 4matic
ah I got some green construction paper
that I'll be using for my mana cost on
so I thought I'd just throw a little
heads up because you know I have a bunch
of Manic ‘ns on my tail so peace out